In the last video, we instantiated
在上个视频中
a LinearLearner model and I want to quickly go over how we formatted the training data.
我们实例化了一个 LinearLearner 模型 下面简单讲解下我是如何格式化训练数据的
Essentially, I want to take the train features and labels that were generated from
我希望将 split_data 函数生成的训练特征和标签
my split data function above and turn them into
转换成 RecordSet
a record set that my estimator can use for training.
并作为 estimator 可以使用的训练数据
So my first step is going to be converting my features
首先将特征和标签
and my labels into a float 32 type.
转换成 float32 类型
Then I can use a linear.record_set to create a RecordSet out of this data.
然后使用 linear.record_set 将数据转换成 RecordSet 格式
I just have to pass in my features and my labels.
只需传入特征和标签
This may look familiar from when we did this in an unsupervised case.
这与之前的非监督式示例很像
Only in an unsupervised case,
只是在非监督式示例中
we only had to pass in the features.
我们仅传入了特征
This time, since we're doing a supervised learning task,
这次因为我们要执行监督式学习任务
we also have to pass in labels.
所以还需要传入标签
So we have x our features and y are class labels here.
x 表示特征 y 表示标签
This may look familiar from when we created a RecordSet in an unsupervised learning case.
这个看起来与在非监督式学习示例中创建 RecordSet 很像
Only in that case, we only had to pass in our training features.
但当时我们仅传入了训练特征
We didn't have any labels to work with.
我们没有任何标签可以参考
This time, we have to pass in both x our training features and y our training labels,
这次 我们需要传入训练特征 x 和训练标签 y
and this creates a formatted train data.
并创建特殊格式的训练数据
Then to train a model on this formatted data,
然后 为了用特殊格式的数据训练模型
I just have to call linear.fit and pass in the formatted data.
只需调用 linear.fit 并传入特殊格式的数据
This cell creates a training job with some name.
这个单元格将创建一个具有特定名称的训练作业
Launches are required instances and trains are linear estimator.
启动所需的实例并训练线性 estimator
Your next task was to deploy the trained model.
你的下个任务是部署训练过的模型
So as our estimator trained,
在 estimator 训练后
you should have seen a lot of data about the epic that were on,
你应该会看到很多数据 包括当前周期
as well as a few details about how our model is training.
以及关于模型训练的详细信息
As always, I can check on the status of this job by looking in our SageMaker console.
与之前一样 可以在 SageMaker 控制台中查看这个作业的状态
So if I go to my SageMaker console and I click on Training Jobs,
转到 SageMaker 控制台并点击“Training jobs”
I see a lot from my previous work and this one that's in progress.
可以看到我之前执行了很多训练作业 这个是正在运行的作业
So I'm going to click on this one that we just kicked off.
点击我们刚刚启动的这个作业
I should see the job name, its status,
可以看到作业名称 状态
and every details about its creation and type.
甚至还有创建和类型详情
I can even see some of the hyperparameters that are left
某些参数保留为默认值
as either default values or values that I specified,
或采用我指定的值
like the number of epochs and predictor type.
例如周期数和预测器类型
I'm going to monitor this training job by looking at the logs.
打开日志 看看训练作业的状况
The log stream may take a moment to generate,
日志需要一段时间才能生成
but then you should be able to see something like this.
打开后 将看到这样的消息记录
When you click on these logs,
点击这些日志后
you should be able to see a lot of data printed out.
可以看到系统输出了很多数据
We can expand one of these metrics to see the binary classification cross entropy loss.
展开某个指标 看看二元分类交叉熵损失
In this case, we can see that we're training a LinearLearner and we're on the epic zero.
可以看到 我们训练的是 LinearLearner 并且位于第 0 周期
If I scroll further down,
继续向下滚动
I can click on the metrics and look at results from later epics.
点击指标并查看后续周期的结果
But only if I wait till the end of training,
等待训练结束
I should see that a best model was found and a checkpoint was saved.
可以看到系统发现了最佳模型并保存了检查点
If I look a little above this best model line,
往这个最佳模型上面看看
I can look at metrics during training.
可以查看训练过程中的指标
Here, I have the final training loss which is a lot lower than when we started.
这是最终训练损失 比一开始的低多了
Next, I can see the classification accuracy,
接着可以看到分类准确率
which is really high for our training data.
在训练数据上的准确率很高
There's also scores for our training position and our training recall.
还有训练精确率和召回率分数
We'll get into all of these metrics in a bit.
稍后讲解这些指标
All of this was actually printed out in the notebook,
所有这些都会在 notebook 中输出
it's just a lot easier to read in the logs I find.
但是我发现日志读起来方便多了
Now, if you successfully trained your linear estimator,
如果你成功训练了线性 estimator
it's time to deploy it and create a linear_predictor.
就可以部署它并创建线性预测器了
Once you deploy this predictor,
部署该预测器后
you'll be able to use it to make predictions.
你可以使用它做出预测
I suggest you run the next few cells to see
建议运行下面的几个单元格
how the result looks when you pass in some test data.
看看当你传入测试数据后 结果如何
Next, I'll show you a diploid solution and go over some of my test evaluation results.
接下来我将演示我的部署方式并介绍我的一些测试评估结果